https://www.buzzboxdrivingschool.com.au/privacypolicy.html

Buzz Box Privacy Policy
In this policy, "us", "we" or "our" means Buzz Box Driving School (ABN 42907927847).
What This Privacy Policy Covers
We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.
How We Use Your Personal Information
We comply with the Australian Privacy Principles (“APPs”). This Privacy Policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information or opinion about an individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable (whether the information or opinion is true or not, and whether the information or opinion is recorded in a material form) and includes (but is not limited to) the following kinds of information: your name, address, email address, phone number and so on.
By using our products and services, you consent to us using your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection And Use
General
We collect personal information when you use our products or services, when you visit our pages or the pages of certain Buzz Box Driving School partners, and when you enter promotions or competitions. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, post code, license, license expiry and phone. When you register with us you are not anonymous to us.
We collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.
We automatically receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.
Information Sharing And Disclosure
Buzz Box Driving School does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We provide the information, in compliance with the Australian Privacy Principles, to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Buzz Box Driving School under confidentiality agreements. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information, except to the extent required by law. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Buzz Box Driving School terms of conditions, or as otherwise required by law.
On some occasions your personal information may need to be transferred to overseas countries including the United States, in order to perform one or more of Buzz Box Driving School functions or activities and you consent to such transfer and acknowledge that Section 8.1 of the Australian Privacy Principles will not apply to such transfer.
Cookies
We may set and access our cookies on your computer.
Buzz Box Driving School lets other companies that track usage on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Other companies do not have access to Buzz Box Driving School cookies.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Buzz Box Driving School service, such as appointments or administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
You may also request access to and correction of the personal information Buzz Box Driving School holds about you by writing to the Privacy Officer.
Confidentiality And Security
We limit access to personal information about you to our employees or those of our related bodies corporate who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions, Complaints And Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form. Complaints about a breach of the APPs must be addressed in writing to:
Privacy Officer
Buzz Box Driving School
PO Box 302
YINNAR
VIC 3869 Australia
We will notify you within 14 working days of the Privacy Officer receiving your complaint and will try to resolve the complaint within 30 working days. When this is not possible we will contact you to provide an estimate of the time it will take to resolve the complaint.
Home (current)
Prices
Bookings
Area Coverage
Contact
License Info
Driving Tips
Quick Quiz
Graduates
Buzz Box Privacy Policy
In this policy, "us", "we" or "our" means Buzz Box Driving School (ABN 42907927847).
What This Privacy Policy Covers
We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.
How We Use Your Personal Information
We comply with the Australian Privacy Principles (“APPs”). This Privacy Policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information or opinion about an individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable (whether the information or opinion is true or not, and whether the information or opinion is recorded in a material form) and includes (but is not limited to) the following kinds of information: your name, address, email address, phone number and so on.
By using our products and services, you consent to us using your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection And Use
General
We collect personal information when you use our products or services, when you visit our pages or the pages of certain Buzz Box Driving School partners, and when you enter promotions or competitions. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, post code, license, license expiry and phone. When you register with us you are not anonymous to us.
We collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.
We automatically receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.
Information Sharing And Disclosure
Buzz Box Driving School does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We provide the information, in compliance with the Australian Privacy Principles, to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Buzz Box Driving School under confidentiality agreements. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information, except to the extent required by law. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Buzz Box Driving School terms of conditions, or as otherwise required by law.
On some occasions your personal information may need to be transferred to overseas countries including the United States, in order to perform one or more of Buzz Box Driving School functions or activities and you consent to such transfer and acknowledge that Section 8.1 of the Australian Privacy Principles will not apply to such transfer.
Cookies
We may set and access our cookies on your computer.
Buzz Box Driving School lets other companies that track usage on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Other companies do not have access to Buzz Box Driving School cookies.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Buzz Box Driving School service, such as appointments or administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
You may also request access to and correction of the personal information Buzz Box Driving School holds about you by writing to the Privacy Officer.
Confidentiality And Security
We limit access to personal information about you to our employees or those of our related bodies corporate who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions, Complaints And Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form. Complaints about a breach of the APPs must be addressed in writing to:
Privacy Officer
Buzz Box Driving School
PO Box 302
YINNAR
VIC 3869 Australia
We will notify you within 14 working days of the Privacy Officer receiving your complaint and will try to resolve the complaint within 30 working days. When this is not possible we will contact you to provide an estimate of the time it will take to resolve the complaint.
